[Music]
[Música]
Okay, now the intro. Now the intro too, I would
bueno ya la intro ahora la intro también
play it a little. I would take the
la re tocaría un poco le quitaba el
dog off the corner. I find it a little
perro de la esquina lo veo un poco poco
unaesthetic. I find it a little unaesthetic. It's a little unaesthetic. I
estético lo veo un poco estético es un
see it a little unaesthetic. I
poco poco estético lo veo un poco poco
see it, but well, things are
estético lo veo pero bueno las cosas se
polished when they feel like it and by
van puliendo cuando ellos le apetezca y
doing other things, among other things, well,
haciendo otras entre otras cosas pues
we see them and we choose and we choose. Okay,
las vemos y elegimos y elegimos vale
well, let's see, honestly, I wasn't thinking about being
bueno a ver sinceramente no pensaba ser
direct. In fact, I didn't even remember to
directo de hecho ni me he acordado de
plug in. I was
enchufar
n't thinking about being direct because I had a debate. I
no pensaba ser directo porque tenía un
had a debate tonight
debate tenía un debate de esta noche
with the PP. We
con el pp nos
needed salt. Xeito, the king of salsa,
hacía falta sal xeito el rey del salsero
smiling face with horns, I love you gesture. I
cara sonriendo con cuernos gesto de te
know a lot of things happen in the purge,
sé que pasan muchas cosas en la purga
but I've told people,
pero le he dicho a la gente
Karim, Idn, and Paula, not to
a karim e idn a paula que menos
collect much. But to record it tomorrow
recopilen pero para grabarlo mañana por
morning to upload the main one to
la mañana para subir la principal para
be a main video, okay, let's
ser un videito principal vale vamos a
record a couple of things for the
a grabar un par de cositas para el
secondary one. But today I had a
secundario pero es que hoy tenía un
debate. Well, it's not that today they had
debate bueno no es que hoy tuvieron
debates that three days ago, I had a
debates que hace ya tres días tenía un
debate last week that in the end didn't
debate la semana pasada que al final no
appear, it couldn't be done.  do marc and
apareció no se pudo hacer marc y locuras
mediocre craziness I ivo that no
mediocres ivo que no
that I couldn't win anything time I don't know what
que no podía ganar nada tiempo no sé qué
and now the tp resurrection that one who
y ahora el tp resurrección ese que se
fought with the one who has me the most sector debate
peleó con la q más me ha sector debate
in theory opened a
en teoría me abrió por
private message with me and I tell you that
privado y os digo que va a estar muy
the debate is going to be very good I have many things to
bueno el debate tengo muchas cosas que
tell him but there he left me stranded he doesn't
decirle pero allí me dejó tirado no me
answer my DMs he sent me a DM at 8
contesta a los md me mandó un md a las 8
in the morning telling me that here
de la mañana diciéndome es que aquí en
where I live it is a different time than
donde yo vivo es otra hora diferente que
yours well listen to me kid now in
la tuya bueno escucharme chico ahora en
Colombia now in Colombia I think it's
colombia ahora en colombia creo que son
like 7 to 8 in the evening we're going to
como las 7 a las 8 de la tarde vamos a
talk I do
hablar
n't know how to confirm the time it is in
no sé confirmarme la hora que es en
Colombia I think that's like 7 to 8
colombia creo que eso como las 7 a las 8
in the evening right now it's not good I'm
de la tarde ahora mismo no es bueno lo
going to wait a little longer I know that a
voy a esperar un ratito más ya sé que un
little more time I'm going to do a couple
poquito más de tiempo voy a hacer un par
of excerpts
de extractos
the microphone is great look now I can
el micro estupendo mira ya lo puedo
move it calmly that's what
mover tranquilo que es para lo que sirve
the arm is for look at the microphone god
el brazo mira en el micro dios
but because everyone was fighting a
pero porque todo el mundo se peleaba una
comma well because it's striking
coma bueno porque es llamativa
let's call it that it's 6  in the afternoon
llamémoslo así son las 6 de la tarde
well I don't know why that boy wants to
pues no sé por qué ese chico quiere
debate at nine in the morning from here
debatir a las nueve de la mañana de aquí
at eight nine in the morning from here if it's
a las ocho nueve de la mañana de aquí si
very late there you
es muy tarde allí
are listening to that I do
estás escuchando eso
n't know if you get to hear it
no sé si llegáis a escucharlo
they are doing works on the road
están haciendo obras en la carretera
below my house like opening the
abajo de mi casa en plan abriendo la
road
carretera
if they get used to leaving here I really
si se usan de irme de aquí de verdad lo
say it well let's see and I tell you I tell you let's
digo bueno a ver y os digo os digo vamos
see the premiere well the premiere of
a ver el estreno bueno el estreno de
Rubios en Tortilla no in the end
rubios en tortilla la no al final
we accept we accept I promise you that I didn't
aceptamos aceptamos os prometo que no
know anything it was simply because of the tweet
sabía nada simplemente era por el tweet
the lemon
el limón
is that it doesn't add up to me anything other than
es que no me cuadra otra cosa que no
the lemon 4k but in the end it was the
fuera el limón 4k pero al final era el
rugby player okay let's see the
rugbier vale vamos a ir viendo la
reaction of the people who have been
reacción de la gente que ha dado que
talking about each or what to talk about
hablar cada o que hablar
2020 mind hangers
2020 mente perchas
let's take a look you and I and now we'll see
echemos un vistazo tú y yo y ahora vemos
the others okay
los demás vale
wait from here a minute please
espera de aquí un minuto por favor
anxious
ansioso
a minute
un minuto
if possible
si se puede
they are very violent
están muy violentos
my god there
dios mío
were people what is this because there is
que había gente que es esto porque hay
a camp
un campamento
tree with lemons
árbol con limones
but it is a house look up
pero es una casa mira arriba
but why do you want to light the fire
pero por qué quieres prender el fuego
you have the lighter and they surrounded  hangers
tienes el mechero y cercaron de perchas
that you hear you have the lighter and you can
que se escucha tienes el mechero y se
see I wanted to set fire to it,
percibe ya le quería meter fuego
blond. Hello,
rubio hola
yes, reviews,
si reviews
hello, we ca
hola
n't hear you but it's you.
no te escuchamos pero soy vosotros
A portal has opened and we
se ha abierto un portal y hemos
appeared here. Who are you?
aparecido aquí tú quién eres
The son of a [ __ ] is asked,
se pide al [__]
advanced, advanced,
avanzada avanzada
this manages to destroy everything,
esto logra destruir entera
advance. Supposedly, what's on the
avancen se supone que eso que hay en los
trees are lemons.
árboles son limones
Supposedly, what's on the
se supone que esto que hay en los
trees were lemons. Well, you know
árboles eran limones bueno pues sabéis
that people have rationed. Being the
que que la gente ha racionado siendo
people, I always feel like,
la gente siempre siento como
look, it turns out that blond posted this
mira resulta ser que el rubio puso este
tweet this afternoon when he started live,
tweet esta tarde cuando iniciaba directo
okay, well,
vale bueno
well, this is from the 25th to the 25th, Karim, they
bueno esto es del 25 hasta el 25 karim
've mixed it up. Let's go, we're going to
el han mezclado vamos lo vamos a
comment on it anyway. But this isn't from
comentar igualmente pero esto no es de
blond's entry. This isn't the
la entrada del rubio esto no es la
reaction of the people. This is a live broadcast in
reacción de la gente esto es un directo
which blond people
que el rubios
are cleaning up. Gref Auron and
socas e iban limpiando a gref auron y
Juan are interacting with him all week,
juan interactuando con él toda la semana
and even blond people are coming in to give him
y hasta rubios entrando para darle
interactions. This is murkier and more
interacciones esto es más turbio y
disappointing than I imagined. A worker,
decepcionante de lo imaginado un obrero
what do I do there?
qué hago yo ahí
can say. I've told you how
yo yo puedo decir yo os he dicho cómo
I would act. How do the others act? I'm already on the
actuaría yo ya como actúen los demás
ground.  I ca
ya como a suelo demás
n't do anything else
no puedo hacer otra cosa
this is a string they weren't there I didn't
esto es un string no estuvieron yo no me
find out if I hadn't liked to
enteré si no me hubiera gustado
participate I would have also participated I mean I
participar también hubiera participado
know they don't want me it's not my thing why
o sea yo sé que no me quieren llama para
these things don't appeal to me I started
que estas cosas no me llama empecé en el
there because I don't hang out with them or
lugar porque no me junto con ellos ni
anything no but man if it's for a good
nada no pero hombre si es para una buena
cause they can always count on me for whatever it
causa pueden contar conmigo siempre para
is okay they all went
lo que sea vale se pusieron todos en
live to play let's go out to raise
directo a jugar a salgáis para recaudar
money for La Palma if I was going to
dinero para la palma si yo lo iba a
know I'm in I'll introduce myself and tell them
saber me apunto me presento y les digo
that I'm also in it not the things that
que yo también estoy not las cosas que
Rubio says in this tweet we're going to help
pone rubios este tuit vamos a ayudar con
La Palma with whatever we can all the
lo que se pueda a la palma todos los
SUVs beats and ads today will go towards
suvs beats y anuncios de hoy irán
it at the end of the string
destinados a ello al terminar string
we do calculations let's go ok
hacemos cálculos let's go ok nosotros
when we finish the stream whatever the
cuando terminamos el stream sea en la
platform it is it shows you
plataforma que sea te aparece
how the live went we
cómo ha ido el directo estas pantallas
've published these screens many times damn
las hemos publicado muchas veces ostia
great live and look at an average of so
pues gran directo y mira una media de
many viewers
tantos espectadores
so much money in bits and so much money in
tanto dinero en bits y tanto dinero en
their ok
sus ok
and people say I hope the news from
y dice la gente ojalá las noticias de
Spain talks about the help that
españa hablen de la ayuda que da el
Rubio gives just like when they criticized him
rubio al igual que cuando lo criticaron
for leaving for  Andorra of
por irse para andorra
course if you are there you are there the
claro que si estás tú estás tú que las
news in Spain says that the media
noticias en españa dicen eso los medios
is almost all the majority of media
son casi toda la mayoría de medios
leaning towards the left leaning towards
tirando para izquierda tirando para
leftists and this one jumps out no if he paid
izquierdistas y salta este no si pagase
his taxes in Spain
sus impuestos en españa no haría falta
his alms would not be necessary look at the
su limosna fíjate la
[ __ ] and the [ __ ] and the
gilipollez y la y la chorrada y los
mercenaries that these people are you can't
mercenarios que son esta gente no puede
call it something I can't I would
llamarlo algún modo no puedo yo lo
call it in your hands but look at the
llamaría en tus manos pero fíjate los
mercenaries no
mercenarios no
in the first place
en primer lugar
the fact that Ruby pays a tribute in
el hecho de que ruby un tributo en
Andorra
andorra
because she feels like it
lo hace porque le sale de la [__]
because it interests her more because her work
porque le interesa más porque su trabajo
can be done wherever she wants to
puede hacerlo donde quiera
be and more comfortably people bother her
estar y más a gusto la gente le molesta
less on the street she can live more
menos por la calle puede vivir más
peacefully
tranquilo
now she makes a string to donate
que ahora haga un string para donar
to La Palma we
a la palma
must be grateful not criticize him okay
hay que agradecerlo no criticarlo vale
even though Ruben doesn't pay his taxes in
aunque rubén no pague sus impuestos en
Spain because it doesn't come to him support
españa porque no le sale del apoye
because he doesn't live here he has paid them
porque no vive aquí los ha pagado
for many years there are
durante muchos años
many other youtubers who do
existimos otros muchísimos youtubers que
pay taxes in Spain
sí que pagamos impuestos en españa
okay and that does not mean that it is not necessary to
vale y eso no hace que no haga falta
collect for La Palma to collect for  the
recopila para la palma recaudar para la
palm because because
palma porque porque el dinero de
our tax money is wasted it is
nuestros impuestos se malgasta lo
wasted by politicians a lot of
malgastan los políticos un montón de
advisors a lot of public cars
asesores un montón de coches públicos
nannies out there
niñera por ahí
black payments out there some
pagos en negro por ahí unas dietas
impressive allowances out there lifetime payments out
impresionantes por ahí pagas vitalicias
there okay they take half of me they
por ahí vale a mí me quitan la mitad
take half of me practically
a mí me quitan la mitad prácticamente
euro up euro down it is the calculation of
euro arriba euro abajo es el cálculo de
what I generated last year
lo que genere el año pasado
also you know what
además que sabéis qué
because you probably don't know but us
porque seguramente no lo sepáis pero los
youtubers are precisely the
youtubers somos precisamente
ones who have the clearest idea of the
los que más claros tenemos las
declarations of all of us who earn
declaraciones de todos los que ganamos
because because we collect everything by
porque porque todo lo cobramos por por
bank transfer
transferencia bancaria
so maybe
entonces
you have a fruit shop or you
tú a lo mejor tienes una frutería o
have a
tienes una
tattoo shop or you have a
un negocio de tatuaje o tienes un
business of
negocio de
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
hicks thank you very much thank you
hicks muchas gracias muchas gracias
maybe you have a tattoo shop
a lo mejor tienes un negocio de tatuaje
or whatever and at least if they pay you in
o lo que sea y a lo menos si te pagan en
cash there is a part there the
manos en metálico hay parte ahí la
majority of businesses people pay taxes
mayoría de negocio la gente tributa
feed what they want
alimente lo que le sale de la [__]
many people do it well not the majority
mucha gente lo hace bueno no la mayoría
but many people do no I mean well
pero mucha gente lo hace no
this goes to dad dad knows
o sea pues esto va para papá papá sabe
but what is he what are the youtube
pero lo que es el lo que son los youtube
all those collected by transfer
todos los cobrados por transferencia
banking so everything is
bancaria por lo tanto todo queda
recorded and you don't get away with anything okay and
registrado y no te libras ni una vale y
I don't earn an impressive amount of money
yo que no cobró un dinero impresionante
because the truth is I earn money
porque la verdad cobro dinero
from what I worked in the factories let's see
de lo que trabajaba las fábricas demos
that blondes are from Norway not from Spain that
que rubios es de noruega no de españa
those other ones those
que esas otras
others that are too much too much has paid
esas otras que es demasiado demasiado ha
taxes in Spain during all these
tributado en españa durante todos estos
years be it the dull blonde
años sea el rubio apagado
millions and millions and
millones y millones y millones y
millions and millions of euros but come on
millones y millones de euros pero vamos
I did the math last year and I
que yo hice la cuenta el año pasado y yo
am surely one of those who earn the least
soy seguramente de los que menos cobren
I don't earn millions like these people are left over
yo no cobro millonadas como sobran esta
I don't earn millions like these people I
yo no cobro millonada como esta gente yo
earn
cobro un sueldo que está bien un sueldo
a salary that is good a salary that is powerful enough to live quietly not to be rich not to buy myself a mansion or to buy myself a spectacular house or to buy myself a Maserati or anything like that well better than when I was working a salary more in decent ways but even so
sueldo más en condiciones pero aún así
you add up the taxes that I paid
tú sumas los impuestos que pagó al tri
quarterly plus what I paid annually plus the photo
mes más lo que pagó el anual más la foto
self-employed and doing the math
autónomos y haciendo cuentas
honestly
sinceramente
and the account is made recently that it would have been better if I had
y se la cuenta hace poco que mejor que
n't done it from what I generate to what
no lo hubiera hecho de lo que genere a
I have left taking away the taxes
lo que me quede quitándole los impuestos
or  minus half exactly but come on it's
o menos la mitad exactamente pero vamos
almost half it's not
viene siendo casi la mitad no es la
half at least 40 or 39 percent
mitad lo menos un 40 o un 39 por ciento
or crazy amounts a lot okay
o burradas una burrada vale
and I work a lot I would
y yo trabajo mucho
do a lot of thanks so like
haría muchísimas gracias entonces como
I used to go there it's in Spain and a
yo muchísimo iba ahí está en españa y un
lot of it there are a lot of
montonazo es que hay un montonazo de
youtubers who earn a lot of money
youtubers que ganan muchísimo dinero
they are in Spain you
están en españa
know but what happens is that
sabe pero que lo que pasa es que el
money is managed more so what are
dinero se gestiona más entonces que
we going to blame the blond guy for
vamos a culpar al rubio de que haga
needing his money for the palm
falta su dinero para la palma
that wouldn't be necessary his lemon will be taxed
que no haría falta su limón se tributará
in Spain even if the blond guy paid taxes in
en españa' aunque el rubio tributarse en
Spain that money would be wasted on
españa ese dinero sea mal gastaría en
shitty politicians
políticos de [__]
and lifetime payments because the [ __ ] do they have to
y en pagas vitalicias porque [__] tienen
have a lifetime payment a turkey who
que tener una paga vitalicia un pavo que
works
trabaja
45 years in a government in a ministry
45 años en un gobierno en un ministerio
why is
por qué
this to be
esto es de ser
while people like this continue to exist
mientras que sigue existiendo gente como
the government will continue to take you for
esta el gobierno seguirá tomando por
idiots
[__]
gorgeous Alejandra Rubio is gorgeous I just
guapísima alejandra rubio es guapísima
made a video of her that's
es que acabo de hacer un vídeo de ella
why the whole photo I won't defend the
por eso toda la foto yo no defenderé al
blond guy but he has paid taxes for
rubio pero ha pagado impuestos por
several generations together at the same time did you
varias generaciones juntas a la vez se
imagine  what the blond guy will earn, he will
imaginaron lo que ganará el rubio que
earn
ganará
a few million euros a year,
unos cuantos de millones de euros al año
surely
seguro
and half of those few million a
y la mitad de esos cuantos millones al
year have gone there
año se han ido para allá
and they come to throw it in his face that the
y se viene a echarle en cara en el
kid has left, now he was up in arms,
chaval se ha ido ahora estaba por culo
I wish he had stayed to continue
ojalá se hubiera quedado para seguir
contributing but he will have his
aportando pero tendrá sus motivos
personal reasons, it's that we have already
personales es que es que esto ya lo
talked about this if the taxes
hemos hablado si los impuestos lo
were to be
pusiera
paid at 15, 20%, 15,
a que se pagará un 15 un 20% un 15 un
20% they would surely stay although well
20% se quedaban seguramente aunque bueno
the one who is there also influences that they are
también influye el que está en que están
more relaxed there,
allí más tranquilos
in short, life is not there, there is no crime, it is going
en fin se vive no hay delincuencia está
very well apparently filling
se está muy bien por lo visto a llenando
organs
órganos
if Spain took care of its citizens who
si españa cuidar a sus ciudadanos que
generate millions it would not have had to
generan millones no se tendría que haber
leave completely it is that in the end
ido totalmente es que al final la gente
when people start earning money,
cuando empieza a ganar dinero en la que
the people who earn millions leave, the people who
se va la gente que gana millones en la
leave, the
que se va
humble and hard-working people are left with more
humilde y trabajadora con trabajos más
humble jobs, let's say with jobs that pay
humildes digamos con trabajos que cobran
a little money and they are suffocated,
un poquito dinero y están asfixiados
yes, I think that what happened in La Palma is the
sí creo que lo que pasó en la palma es
fault of the  blond
culpa del rubios
if I did it you would give a [ __ ]
si lo hiciera te importaría una [__]
just as it should be leave the subject
tal y como debería ser deja el tema
man because the truth is that
hombre pues la verdad que ha hecho
that man has made quite a fool of himself no but
bastante el ridículo ese hombre no pero
well let's see if blond let's see
bueno vamos a ver si rubio vamos a ver
if blonds
si rubios
blonds usually abandon the series not
rubinos suele abandonar las series no
al qadi in the end he wasn't
al qadi al abandono al final no le
very motivated by the game but it's that it doesn't
motivaba mucho el juego pero es que no
motivate them from the beginning either no
les motiva desde el principio tampoco no
I would tell myself the truth well look no maybe I would
yo me diría la verdad pues mira no a lo
n't tell you rocio but me I would
mejor no te diría rocío pero yo yo me
leave if I were
iría si estuviera
single but if we had my wife
los solteros sino si tuviéramos mi mujer
and I alone if we left for
y yo solo si nos íbamos
sure because the years that
seguro porque es que los años que dure
this lasts the years that this lasts we could
esto los años que dure esto podríamos
save a lot of money and then not
ahorrar muchísimo dinero para luego no
work and I'm not talking about millions I'm
trabajar y no te hablo de millonada
talking about saving money to live
hablo de ahorrar dinero para vivir
normally and humbly a normal apartment a
normal y humildemente piso normal un
normal car well a normal car a
coche normal bueno un coche normal una
normal life not for the rich you
vida normal no de ricos
understand
me entendéis
but it doesn't matter that it doesn't matter even if
pero es que da igual que dé igual aunque
the rich and even if those who generate
los ricos y aunque los que generan
millions stayed in Spain
millonadas se quedasen en españa
then that money would not go to the
luego ese dinero no iría destinado a las
things these are destined for their balls
cosas éstas van destinados a sus [__]
and it's shameless that they do with
y es de poca vergüenza que hagan con
our money what they want but  Well,
nuestro dinero lo que quieren pero bueno
this is a fight we've already had. We
esto es una pelea que ya la hemos tenido
've already debated it a lot this year
ya lo hemos debatido mucho este año
when the Andorra issue came up. The issue
cuando salió el tema de andorra el tema
of the blonde is the issue,
del rubio es el tema de
and as long as there are people like that, they
y mientras haya gente así
won't continue to take us for a ride and they'll
no nos seguirán tomando el pelo y se
continue to make fun of us,
seguirán cachondeando de nosotros
and that's what it is.
y eso es lo que hay
[Music]
[Música]